sixjax.com 2011-03-18

# sixjax | Privacy Policy

Sixjax.com (the "Site") is a service provided by Sixjax, LLC ("Sixjax"). We acknowledge and respect your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes how Sixjax gathers information while you're visiting the Site.

Please read this Privacy Policy before using the Site or submitting any personal information. By using the Site, you accept and consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy. By your continued use you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with these practices you are free to discontinue your use of the Site at any time.

If you have questions about our privacy policy, please email us at [support@sixjax.com](mailto:support@sixjax.com).

You may visit the Site at any time without revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit the Site, we may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from the Site, advertisement data, IP address and standard web log information, such as demographic and navigation data.

For you to actively participate in this Site, we do need some of your personal information. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.

When you register on and continue to use the Site, we will collect the following information: email address, first and last name, date of birth, and password; transactional information based on your interaction with the Site; shipping, billing and other information; correspondence sent to us; financial information, such as your credit card information; and other supplemental information.

Our purpose for collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, efficient, and customized experience. By signing up, you agree that we may use your personal information to: provide the services and customer support you request; resolve disputes; collect fees; troubleshoot problems; prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities; enforce our Terms & Conditions; customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; inform you about our services, including targeted marketing, service updates, and promotions; and compare and verify your information with third parties for accuracy.

We may disclose your personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our Terms & Conditions and Privacy Policy, respond to claims that your uploaded content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. 

We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to: fraud investigations; debt collection; law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law; and with other business entities with which we plan to merge with or be acquired by.

We do not share your personal information with third party advertisers.

As you register with the Site, you will be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout the Site and therefore provided to the public. If you win an auction, the Site may display the number of bids and dollar value of those bids when the auction ends. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, other users will not be able to personally identify your activities on the Site.

When visiting the Site from a public or shared computer, your personal information may also be visible to others who use that computer after your use. It is your responsibility to ensure your private information is removed from the public or shared computer should you choose to use one.

You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to the Site at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. Accurate information is required for billing and delivery purposes. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate.

Upon closing your account, Sixjax will remove your information from public view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms & Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.

Sixjax uses so-called "cookies", which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the Site. The information saved in cookies supports the functionality of the Site, for example, by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of "pop-up" windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your computer by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, adjusting these settings may result in limited functionality.

Your Sixjax account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Sixjax will never ask for your password in e-mail or over the phone. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your Internet browser window when you leave the Site; this is especially important if you use a PC in a public location. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.

Sixjax will use your e-mail address only for the purposes stated in the Terms & Conditions and this Privacy Policy. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by "web crawlers" or "web spiders" to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been inappropriately disclosed, please email us at [support@sixjax.com](mailto:support@sixjax.com).

Sixjax is sensitive to the need to protect the privacy of children who use the Internet. Sixjax does not knowingly collect or solicit personally identifiable information from or about children under the age of eighteen (18), consistent with the requirements of the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act. If we discover or are otherwise notified that we have received any such information of a child in violation of this policy, we will delete that information. If you are under the age of eighteen (18), please do not attempt to provide any personally identifiable information via the Site. If you believe that Sixjax has any information from or about a child under the age of thirteen, please contact us immediately by clicking on "Contact Us" and sending us an e-mail and we will take appropriate steps to remove such information from our files.

Please review the privacy policy of other sites you or your children elect to link to through the Site for the children's privacy policies of those sites. Sixjax is not responsible for the privacy policies or other content of any other website, including sites that are co-branded.

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the new Privacy Policy on the Site. Sixjax reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time without notice to you. Consequently, you should review this Privacy Policy for changes each time you visit the Site.

If you have a privacy question about the Site, please email us at [support@sixjax.com](mailto:support@sixjax.com).

Correspondence can be sent to:

Sixjax LLC  
41 E. 11th Street, 11th Floor  
New York, NY 10003
